globalwellnesssummit.com 2018-03-24

# GLOBAL WELLNESS SUMMIT PRIVACY POLICY

                             GLOBAL WELLNESS SUMMIT PRIVACY POLICY
At the Global Wellness Summit (“GWS”) your privacy is important to us. Before submitting
any personal information to our website, please read this Privacy Policy carefully to learn
about our privacy practices. By visiting the GWS website, www.globalwellnesssummit.com,
you are accepting the practices described herein. We may change our Privacy Policy from
time to time. If we do make changes, we will make a notice on our website and post those
changes here so that you will always know what information we gather and how we might
use it.
Table of Contents
1.   Information we collect from you
2.   How we use your information
3.   Who we share your information with
4.   How you can access your information
5.   Security
6.   Children's privacy
7.   External links
8.   Visiting our website from outside the United States
9.   California privacy rights
10. Changes to this Privacy Policy
11. Contact us
1. Information we collect from you
Our site collects both general and personal information. General information may include:
your domain name and host for Internet access; the date and time of your entry; your IP
address, browser type, or operating system; the pages you visit and links that you use; if
you linked to our site from a third party site, the domain name from which you linked to our
site; your zip code; and, other general demographic information. Personal information may
be collected from you in connection with a registration form, an online survey, a
sweepstakes or contest, or other instances when you submit information through our site.
You can choose not to provide information to us, but some information about you may be
required in order for you to register for our annual summit or to enjoy certain benefits of
our site.
We also may periodically obtain both personal and non-personal information about you from
affiliated entities, business partners and other independent third-party sources and add it to
other information about you. For example, if you visit www.globalwellnesssummit.com from
a site operated by one of our business partners, and you have registered with that partner,
then information about you that you have provided to that partner may be shared with us.
Cookies and Other Web Technologies.
Cookies are small data text files and can be stored on your computer’s hard drive (if your
Web browser permits). Our site uses cookies for the following general purposes:

                             GLOBAL WELLNESS SUMMIT PRIVACY POLICY
       To help us recognize your browser as a previous visitor and save and remember any
        preferences that may have been set while your browser was visiting our site. For
        example, if you register on our site, we may use cookies to remember your
        registration information, so you do not need to log into our site each time you visit.
        Please note that member IDs, passwords, and any other account-related data
        included in such cookies are encrypted for security purposes.
       To help us customize the content provided to you on our websites and on other
        websites across the Internet.
       To help measure and research the effectiveness of website features, offerings, and e-
        mail communications (by determining which e-mails you open and act upon).
The “help” portion of the toolbar on most browsers should tell you how to prevent your
browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive
a new cookie, or how to disable most types of cookies. Please note that if you refuse to
accept cookies, you may not be able to access many of the tools offered on our sites.
Our website may also use web beacons (also known as clear gifs, pixel tags or web bugs),
which are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, that are
placed in the code of a webpage. We use web beacons to monitor the traffic patterns of
users from one page within our sites to another, to deliver or communicate with cookies, to
understand whether you have come to our site from an online advertisement displayed on a
third-party website, and to improve site performance. We may also allow our service
providers to use web beacons to help us understand which emails have been opened by
recipients and to track the visitor traffic and other actions on our site.
2. How we use your information
GWS uses the information we collect about you for the following general purposes: for
registration and to facilitate your access to and use of our site; to communicate with you in
general, including to provide information about GWS; to respond to your questions and
comments; to measure interest in and improve our products, services, and website; to
notify you about information that may be of interest to you; to solicit information from you,
including through surveys; to resolve disputes or troubleshoot problems; to prevent
potentially prohibited or illegal activities; to enforce our Terms of Use; and as otherwise
described to you at the point of collection.
3. Who we share your information with
GWS may share your information with the following entities:
       Third-party vendors who provide services or functions on our behalf, including
        business analytics, customer service, marketing, distribution of surveys or
        sweepstakes programs, and fraud prevention. We may also authorize third-party
        vendors to collect information on our behalf, including as necessary to operate
        features of our website or to facilitate the delivery of online advertising tailored to
        your interests. Third-party vendors have access to and may collect information only
        as needed to perform their functions and are not permitted to share or use the
        information for any other purpose.
       Business partners with whom we may offer products or services in conjunction. You
        can tell when a third party is involved in a product or service you have requested
        because their name will appear either with ours or separately. If you choose to
        access these optional services, we may share information about you, including your

                            GLOBAL WELLNESS SUMMIT PRIVACY POLICY
        personal information, with those partners. Please note that we do not control the
        privacy practices of these third-party business partners.
       Referring websites. If you were referred to our site from another website, we may
        share your registration information, such as your name, email address, mailing
        address, telephone number and travel preferences, about you with that referring
        website. We have not placed limitations on the referring websites’ use of personal
        information and we encourage you to review the privacy policies of any website that
        referred you to SpaFinder.
       Social Media Services. You can choose to access certain third party social media
        websites and services through our site (such as Facebook). When you do so, you are
        sharing information with those sites, and the information you share will be governed
        by their privacy policies. You may also be able to modify your privacy settings with
        these third party social media websites.
We also may share your information:
       In response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process; to establish or
        exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by
        law. In such cases we reserve the right to raise or waive any legal objection or right
        available to us.
       When we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding
        illegal or suspected illegal activities; to protect and defend the rights, property, or
        safety of SpaFinder, our customers, or others; and in connection with our Terms of
        Service and other agreements.
       In connection with a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, merger,
        consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.
4. How you can access, update, or delete your information
We take reasonable steps to ensure that your information is relevant to its intended use,
accurate, and complete. You can access and update your contact information by logging in
to your account on the GWS website. Please also note that we may retain certain
information associated with your account in our archives, including for analytical purposes
as well as for recordkeeping integrity.
5. Security
We are committed to protecting the information we collect. While no website can guarantee
security, we have implemented appropriate administrative, technical, and physical security
procedures to help protect the personal information you provide to us. For example, only
authorized employees are permitted to access personal information, and they only may do
so for permitted business functions. In addition, we use encryption when transmitting your
personal information between your system and ours, and we employ firewalls and intrusion
detection systems to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your
information.
6. Children's privacy
The GWS website is intended for general audiences site and is not directed to children under
13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you become
aware that a child has provided us with personal information without parental consent,
please contact us at webmaster@globalwellnesssummit.com. If we become aware that a

                            GLOBAL WELLNESS SUMMIT PRIVACY POLICY
child under 13 has provided us with personal information without parental consent, we take
steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account.
7. External links
If any part of the GWS website links you to other websites, those external websites do not
operate under this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you examine the privacy statements
posted on those other websites to understand their procedures for collecting, using, and
disclosing personal information.
8. Visiting our websites from outside the United States
If you are visiting our website from outside the United States, please be aware that your
information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our
servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other
laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in
your country, but please be assured that GWS does take steps pursuant to laws in the
United States to ensure that your privacy is protected. By using our services, you
understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties
with whom we share it as described in this Policy.
9. California privacy rights
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California residents to request certain
information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct
marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us at
spafinder@webmaster.com.
10.Changes to this Privacy Policy
GWS may update this Privacy Policy in the future. We will notify our members about
material changes to this Privacy Policy by placing a notice on our website.
11.Contact Us
If you believe that GWS has not adhered to this Privacy Policy you may write to us at the
following address:
  Global Wellness Summit, LLC
  Attn: Legal Department
  257 Park Avenue South
  New York, NY 10010
  United States of America
If you have general questions about this Privacy Policy, please email us at
webmaster@globalwellnesssummit.com or you may also contact us at:
  Global Wellness Summit, LLC
  Attn: Privacy Policy
  257 Park Avenue South
  New York, NY 10010

                             GLOBAL WELLNESS SUMMIT PRIVACY POLICY
©2015 Global Wellness Summit, LLC. All rights reserved.
This Privacy Policy is effective as of April 11, 2013.
